

# **Personal Info**

Name: Jasper Carter

Address: Eastern Suburbs,

Melbourne

DOB: 14.12.1997

**Age:** 22

Gender: Male

#### **Contact**

PH: 0408018904

Email: jaspercarter1997

@hotmail.com

# Skills

Adobe CC 365 Apps Jira HTML/CSS JavaScript React JS SAP AD Service

PHP

Lync

Workpace1

Node.JS

Ionic

SQL

### Experience

Intermediate
Intermediate
Intermediate
Intermediate
Intermediate
Beginner
Intermediate
Beginner
Intermediate
Beginner
Intermediate
Beginner
Intermediate
Intermediate
Intermediate

Beginner

## **RESUME**

#### About me

Inquisitive IT support/administrator with 2 years of industry experience. Having worked for a medical company within IT, now looking to grow my career further. Learning most of my IT skills with experience and by obtaining knowledge from my own studies. Also completing a Diploma of Digital Media at Torrens University and have previously studied IT at Macquarie University. I am a hardworking, driven, ambitious and passionate worker looking to further my career.

## Experience

2020 - Present

#### Reesby

Intern Front-end developer/ Part-time

- Design and create web-pages with ReactJS
- Research and work with API's
- Developing an app with React/Ionic
- Working with small teams on different projects.
- Working remotely

2018 - Present

#### **Device Technologies AU**

IT Support/ Administrator

- Providing lvl1 lvl3 support to the internal business.
- Administering Active Directory, Exchange, Lync and UniFlow.
- Administering server environments.
- Managing company voice and data services (with the help of a 3 man helpdesk team).
- Updating and maintaining a fleet of Dell computers and mobile devices.
- Creating knowledge Articles and documentation
- Managing external office(VIC) away from Head office(NSW).

#### References

Reesby Anna Maria Adamidis Events

PH: +61 426 911 367 Email: partnerships@reesby.

com.au

Device Technologies AU Marko Denev Manger IT Security PH: +61 429 175 083 Email: mdenev@device.com.

Graham Cronin

Head of IT Email: gcronin@device.com.

au

Merivale - The Newport Jonathan Crofts Bar Manager

PH: +61 427 478 427 Email: jonathan.crofts@

merivale.com

Steven Payne
Bar Training Manager
PH: +61 427 478 427
Email: steven.payne@
merivale.com

Nov 2017 -Dec 2017

### **Sessions Taphouse**

Bartender/ Brewers Assistant

- Operated a lunch and nightclub bar.
- Poured and made a range of drinks from: Beers, Wines, spirits and Cocktails.
- As a brewer making a range of different lagers and Ales from scratch using different grains and hops.

2016 - 2018

### Merivale - The Newport(NSW)

Bartender

- Operated bar at several locations; prepared cocktails, beer, wine, and spirits.
- Utilized knowledge of cocktails, mixed beverages, specialty liquors and craft beers to serve customers with well prepared drinks in a timely fashion.
- Created a welcoming and enjoyable experience ensuring guest satisfaction by maintaining a friendly, accommodating and positive attitude.

# **Education and Training**

2019 - 2020

Diploma of Digital Media Torrens University

2016 - 2017

Unit completion: Data-Base Management, Intro to Digital Media, Intro to computer programming, Academic Communication in Science Macquarie University

2009 - 2015

High School Certificate (HSC) Mater Maria Catholic College